

SHASHI RAMOLA

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

I consider myself to be a versatile artist. I have a strong hand in software like Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Coreldraw and ADOBE XD. My focus and handwork working nature are what complement my conceptualization skills. My expertise includes in the field of social media posts creatives. I have always been a team player. Hard work and quality work is what define me.

I am always ready to face new obstacles. I like to know the latest trends in my field. Ready to do productive work each day.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2022 IGNOU

Master's in Eng. Hons.

2017 - 2020 Kalindi college

BA Programme

2017 - 2018 Envision Institute Advance Diploma in Graphics and Web Designing

2015 - 2017 Kendriya vidyalaya

10th and 12th from cbse

EXPERIENCE

Dec 2022 - Present Graphic Designer

Stealth Technocrats

Jan 2019 - Dec 2022 Graphic Designer

Only For Solution

Jan 2018 - April 2018 Graphic Designer

Internship in Envision institute

LANGUAGE

English Hndi

CONTACT ME



BIRTHDAY 17 jan 1999



WEB shashiramola1999@gmail.com



PHONE 8383950128



ADDRES Mundka, Delhi-110081

PRO SKILLS

Graphic Designing

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR CAMTASIA

COREL DRAW POWTOON ADOBE XD

AFTER EFFECTS PREMIERE PRO

Infographic
Social Media Creatives for Fb, Insta,
Pinterest, Twitter
Icons
Logo
2d video
Video Editing
Web Page Templates
Email Templates/ Newsletter
Brochures
Flyers







